{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Avengers: Endgame with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who wields Mjolnir?",
      "answers": ["Thor", "Hulk", "Loki"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sacrifices for the Soul Stone?",
      "answers": ["Nat", "Tony", "Thor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who fights Thanos first?",
      "answers": ["Thor", "Hulk", "Tony"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Hulk's form?",
      "answers": ["Smart", "Rage", "Gray"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the time heist leader?",
      "answers": ["Cap", "Tony", "Nat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Tony's daughter's name?",
      "answers": ["Morgan", "Pepper", "Nat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who returns the stones?",
      "answers": ["Cap", "Thor", "Tony"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who lifts Mjolnir besides Thor?",
      "answers": ["Cap", "Hulk", "Loki"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Black Widow's weapon?",
      "answers": ["Staves", "Shield", "Sword"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who gets the Time Stone?",
      "answers": ["Hulk", "Thor", "Cap"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Vormir?",
      "answers": ["Space", "Earth", "Asgard"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rocket's partner?",
      "answers": ["Thor", "Hulk", "Groot"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who becomes Ronin?",
      "answers": ["Clint", "Tony", "Thor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who leads Wakanda?",
      "answers": ["T'Challa", "Shuri", "Okoye"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Tony's suit number?",
      "answers": ["85", "50", "42"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who does Cap dance with?",
      "answers": ["Peggy", "Sharon", "Nat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who destroys the stones?",
      "answers": ["Thanos", "Hulk", "Tony"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who fights past Cap?",
      "answers": ["Cap", "Bucky", "Nat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who wields Stormbreaker?",
      "answers": ["Thor", "Cap", "Hulk"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who snaps last?",
      "answers": ["Tony", "Hulk", "Cap"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
